<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Generated by Site-Server on Tue, 08 Jul 2025 06:29:38 GMT
--><rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://www.rssboard.org/media-rss" version="2.0"><channel><title>Blog - Indic Software Solutions</title><link>https://indicsoftware.github.io/blog/</link><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 13:35:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><language>en-IN</language><generator>Site-Server</generator><description><![CDATA[]]></description><item><title>We are hiring a Ruby on Rails Developer - 100% Remote</title><dc:creator>Akshat Kedia</dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 13:42:56 +0000</pubDate><link>https://indicsoftware.github.io/blog/we-are-hiring-a-ruby-on-rails-developer-100-remote</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5e205796fa3e61153e82d36e:5e28884928786a6ce09ddf1e:6050b40e1212aa40fdb7061a</guid><description><![CDATA[<p class="">We are excited to announce that we are hiring our first employee: a Ruby on Rails developer.</p><p class=""><strong>About the Job</strong></p><p class="">As a Ruby on Rails developer  you will be working along a designer and will be responsible for  driving projects from concept to a working solution. This is where you  will spend the bulk of your time, but there will also be a fair share of  work doing supporting work like maintenance, bug fixing, writing  technical documentation.</p><p class=""><strong>About You</strong></p><p class="">We are looking for candidates  with a strong track record of putting Rails to work and bringing product  ideas to life. You should have working knowledge of Ruby, HTML, CSS and  JavaScript.</p><p class="">An Engineering or a Computer Science degree is not  what we are looking for. We care about the work you have done and the  work you can do with us.</p><p class="">We do not have the concept of a Manager at Zenmind. Everyone manages their own time, take ownership and get work done on time.</p><p class="">You will have a gentle onboarding experience and time to learn and grow comfortable with us.</p><p class="">Zenmind is a remote-first company and this is a remote job. We are looking for someone preferably located in India.</p><p class=""><strong>Benefits &amp; Perks</strong></p><ul data-rte-list="default"><li><p class="">Get paid a competitive salary.</p></li><li><p class="">Work at a sustainable pace, with realistic targets.</p></li><li><p class="">Participate in a culture of learning and sharing learnings.</p></li><li><p class="">Remote work. </p></li></ul><p class="">Zenmind Studio is a web design and development company. We  specialize in Ruby on Rails, WordPress, Jekyll, Bridgetown and Shopify.  We have worked on projects for World Wildlife Foundation, MIT Media Lab,  Maker's Asylum, IndiaSpend, Vihara Innovation Network, Khoj  International Artists Association, SCMiND LLC.</p><p class="">Folks looking for short-term contract, part-time engagement and freelancing can also apply.</p><p class="">Please send in your resume with a cover letter to <a href="mailto:akshat@zenmind.studio">akshat@zenmind.studio</a>.</p>]]></description></item></channel></rss>